|||||\\\\\\\\\\\\\
Release-Group "Mania" presents
doramamania
Mania
Alchemy
Shower
Can a nomad be cured?
and make him human, even if he has gone wild?
We're not trying to make him human again.
We're trying to keep him conscious so he can talk.
So you're not trying to save him
When a nomad turns into a souleater, there's no turning back
They are monsters
Or they will feed on human energy,
or they will petrify. One of two
We can't prevent this
Ice stone
I heard that he has Hwangsu's strength
Can a stone stop circulation?
Maybe. But...
people should not use such power under any circumstances
Looks like it's going to rain
And I couldn't use the power of reflectors
It looks like everything will be washed away by the rain
Does the reflector's power disappear when it rains?
The power of the ice stone came from heaven
So heaven can take this power away
Project coordinator and editor: Ria_Lee
Assistant coordinators: Martini, gaarysn
Did she try to call upon the power of heaven,
to hide the stone?
Typesetter translators: Ria_Lee, tommo, Zero_Amamiya
Jin Bu Young
If she were alive, she would become a powerful priestess,
who can control the power of heaven
Are you okay
I'm fine too. You haven't gone wild
The gates above the bowl of constellations opened
- Wasn’t the ceiling always like this?
- No
Everyone thinks so
but they told me that this is not so
Who? Your father?
He said to open the gate above the bowl
maybe only a magician-stargazer
How did this happen?
It seems we did something we shouldn't have
But how?
It's me
I opened the gate
My energy leaked into the water
Like at Gyeongjeongdaeho Lake
and in the mirror of Tosca
My energy has returned thanks to this water
What does lightning strike mean?
A loud sound came from the recording room
There are eunuch Kim and Chan Wook there now
This is the power of the reflector
Same dark energy as when Kil Joo tried to swap bodies
What's happened?
I don't see anything, as in the case of a mirror
Dizzy and nauseous
Jin Mu will come soon, we have to leave
Exactly. door
He closed the door with energy, the bowl of constellations is broken,
and the soulswallower is dead
We have problems
There is an exit for servants next to the constellation bowl
My father led me out through this door
But we will still be in Jeonbugwan
You don't see, but I don't know the way
If we get lost, we will be caught
If we stay here, Jin Mu will come and kill us
I won't win against him
I need to call my savior
- The Savior?
- There is one
His heart will tremble and he will come right away
My savior
Chan Wook, are you kidding me?
Did you hear a loud sound?
Yes, but you said not to come in, so we waited
Yeom Soo, follow me. The others are guarding the door
Chan Wook broke the barrier and escaped
Deputy
Bowl of constellations...
What happened to her?
We need to find him
We can't let him out of here alive
Take the body to the secret room
- No one should see you
- Yes
Close all exits
Find Chan Wook and his maid
If necessary, you can kill them
- Yes
Chan Wook will never get out of this maze
He'll get lost and get caught
Or maybe...
he knew he would get lost so he just hid inside
You almost got it
Are you here?
You broke the barrier that I made
Let's do another one. Fiery
If I set this place on fire,
it will probably be quite hot,
to make you show up
Try to convince me like before, without threats
Why if I have nothing to lose?
You are a criminal who entered here without permission and also broke the cup
And my job is to catch the criminal
I'm the deputy of Gwangju
You are too cruel to the guest who came with a gift
Upset that we turned your friend to stone?
What friend?
There was no one here except you two and me.
Aaaaand... want to hide a stone body?
But what can we do?
- You will be caught
- This won't happen
Because you and your maid will die
Come out
Come out!
Have you seen it?
Lightning struck near Jeonbugwan
Jeonbugwan next to the palace
We need to check if everything is okay
Lightning struck so hard
I hope it's right according to Jin Moo
What a shame
Surely he came here happy,
imagining becoming gwangju
But instead you'll die
You're out of luck
This won't work
If I die
you can easily become gwangju
And this cannot be allowed
What?
Have you heard about yin-yang jade?
This is a pair of red and blue jade
If you pour energy into one stone, the second will feel it
If they're nearby
they will find each other
So what?
One of two stones, blue,
now with the Crown Prince
Cute jade
I got it in exchange for toads
Is he valuable?
So what?
I had red
I poured energy into him, which means His Highness
on the way here now
Will you kill me and take the stone?
I thought so, so I hid the stone
Filled it with energy and hid it
in the robe of a eunuch soul swallower
His Highness is probably now in a hurry to the stone body
Imagine his reaction when he sees this
He will be more than surprised
Jeonbugwan
Chan Wook is somewhere in Jeonbugwan
Don't waste your time killing me
better stop the Crown Prince
I'll be back soon
You still won't be able to escape from here.
- Where is the body?
- In the secret room
If you order, I will take him out of there
Where...
He's not here. This bastard fooled me
Deputy
You ordered not to let anyone in, but there was no choice
What? Is the Crown Prince here?
Yes
So he didn't lie about jade
Deputy
The royal eunuch turned into a soul swallower?
And you tried to secretly kill Chan Wook?
This is a misunderstanding, Your Highness
Have you tried
feed my maid to this soul swallower
Better give a normal explanation for what is happening
You are asking about Cho Chun, who worked
stargazer in Jeonbugwan?
I heard Chang Gang and Cho Chun were close
Yes
They were good friends
Cho Chun visited us often
He was a cheerful and kind person
Cho Chun used dark magic
what destroyed his whole family
He was a good man
I still can't believe this happened
He had a daughter. Did you know her?
Yes, I remember her
She was always with her father, they were close
I heard she was missing
I think
she's dead
Why did you decide this?
Master Chang Gang searched for this girl for a very long time.
If she were alive, he would have found her by now.
Unless it was hidden
Lady Do Hwa Died
This happened to his best friend
Master Chan was not himself then
He blamed himself for both deaths
and suffered a lot
He left the house in search of a friend's daughter
I thought he'd come back when he found her
But...
It's strange that he left home for 20 years to find a girl
I'm starting to suspect that he left
for another reason
If he had found that girl 20 years ago,
her life wouldn't be so hard
And Chang Gang wouldn't feel guilty
"Guilt"?
Are you implying that Master Chan behaved incorrectly towards his friend?
He punished him for dark magic
As a magician, he had to
It doesn't matter how close they were, there was no other way
You can't judge what's true and what's not based on what you've seen.
There's a story behind everything
Fate is woven from stories and relationships
That is, painful relationships
Are the Cho and Chan families over?
Or are you...
Are you saying that that girl is in this house now?
Did Pine Forest find her?
That girl
died
I see
It's a pity
We need to hold her wake.
Maid Kim
You are very kind
This is not a gesture of kindness
I just don't want her spirit to come into this world.
and tormented the young master
What if her spirit is haunting Chang Wook?
We need to get rid of it. This must be an evil spirit
I won't let her stalk him
Evil spirit?
Where is Moo Deok?
Moo Deok?
I sent her to Jeonbugwan on an errand
Are you okay? Can you see?
Yes I see
And you, master?
Are you injured anywhere?
I'm fine
What does it mean if two people keep a matching item?
That they are married or dating
The head of Sosnovy Bor arrived on your orders
You have arrived in Jeonbugwan
give the deputy honey cookies??
Yes. I heard you were fighting over them
Maid Kim didn't want him to be upset,
that's why I came to deliver her package
Pathetic excuse
Head of Sosnovy Bor
and the deputy of Gwangju were fighting over cookies?
Even if this is true, it was worth keeping silent about it
What were you doing in the recording room?
I wanted to see the bowl of constellations
But in the end I saw something that I shouldn’t have
Are you sure you saw a soul swallower?
Yes. He put a barrier around me to hide it
and threw Moo Dok to him so that he could get enough
He's lying
Chan Wook entered the recording room without permission
and broke the cup of constellations
And when he was caught,
started making up all sorts of things about the soul swallower
I'm sure it was a soul swallower
He turned to stone
My maid saw it too
When I arrived I didn't see the body
He probably hid it
Seal all exits
and find the soulswallower before he takes him out
I think the truth will come out when we find the body.
I will call the magicians to inspect Jeonbugwan
This is not possible. I can't let them do this
because of someone's baseless lie
Chan Wook,
was the king's eunuch the soul swallower?
Yes
I saw him with the queen when we had a duel
EUNUCH Oh, who was there that day?
Eunuch Kim. He serves the queen
So, we need to check whether he is in the palace now or not.
Go check it out
There's no need for that
The Queen has arrived!
Greet her
Mother
The deputy told me what happened
I was surprised, so I came in person
Did they really find a soul swallower here?
The eunuch who served you was a nomad
He went wild and petrified here
- Is that so?
- This is not true
No one here has turned to stone
It's a lie
which was invented by Chan Wook
We'll know if it's true or false when we find out where the eunuch is.
Who is this eunuch who supposedly turned to stone?
Eunuch Kim
Eunuch Kim came here with me
Eunuch Kim, come in
This eunuch
did you see
petrified?
Yes
You said he's gone wild
But he stands here alive and well
You're right
He's fine
The only way to resolve this is
bring him back to life
He's fine, completely fine
If this is the power of the ice stone,
this means I can save Moo Deok even if she goes wild
Moo Deok,
we must have made a mistake
Probably the owner
You're right. You lied
He's standing here alive
it turns out I really was lying
He tried to fool everyone
because he broke the cup of constellations
Chan Wook,
is this true?
Yes. Everything I said is a lie
Snuck into Jeonbugwan, smashed the relic,
and then lied to cover it up?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
He is the magician of Sosnovy Bor,
I personally apologize for it
I also apologize to Deputy Jin Moo
Pine forest will fix the bowl
No need
Don't give up
This is the only way we can be held accountable for this.
- It's not worth it
- Your Highness
Let Sosnovy Bor correct the mistake.
Let them, mother
Do as you please
It's time for me to go back
I'll send my people tomorrow
to fix a broken bowl
And now I must return to properly punish the magician,
who lied to the prince and the people of Jeonbugwan
- Forward
- It won’t work that way
Chan Wook will stay here and suffer his punishment
I think so too...
What's going on, Your Highness?
Save my master
If he is taken to Sosnovy Bor,
he will be beaten to death there
Last time
he received a hundred blows
This time it will be worse
Don't let this happen
Moo Deok, that's enough.
I did wrong and I will be punished
I did not show due respect to His Highness
I don't dare ask for mercy
Then let them take you and kill you?
If the head wants it, then yes
Heaven...
You can pick me up
How so, master!
You will die!
You will die if you return to Sosnovy Bor!
I will punish him as required by the rule book.
Hey you. Wait
Chan Wook will be punished
forget about what happened
This is just funny
But
the cookie story is even worse
Head of Pine Forest and Deputy of Gwangju
fighting over cookies?
Just laughter
The stupidest excuse
You're right
But how did the bowl of constellations break?
If lightning strikes,
it means the gate above the bowl has opened
But only those who have mastered Chisa can do this.
It's true
Chan Wook doesn't own Chisu
How did the cup break?
Was there anyone else here who owned Chisu?
It's impossible
We got out of there thanks to you, Moo Deok
If you try to leave, they will stop you
If you decide to stay, they’ll try to drive you away.
So you staged this performance on purpose? Smart
I decided that you won't convince them,
so I intervened without permission
Sorry for intruding
I didn't expect this, so I was surprised
But you're great
Chapter
We didn't lie
We saw how eunuch Kim became wild and petrified
I know they didn't lie
Sometimes I'm not thinking clearly
but I can tell lies from truth
He was petrified, but came to his senses
So they have an ice stone?
Sosnovy Bor for a long time
watching Jin Moo
Everything is as we expected
I guess they have the stone
Did you use the stone to revive me?
His strength is simply amazing
I really feel alive
Did Chang Wook turn you to stone?
The energy suddenly started leaving my body
when I was about to get enough of his maid
Then I lost consciousness
Didn't you see how Chang Wook opened the roof over the bowl of constellations?
No, I haven't seen it
Maybe there was another magician there besides Chan Wook?
There was no
What if Chan Wook has already possessed Chisu?
Maybe he's just hiding it
When he attacked me, he didn't look particularly skilled.
He mastered Ryusu in an incredibly short time
Therefore it is possible
Now I have an ice stone inside me,
does this mean I own Hwangsu?
You really have that much power
But you can't cast spells
so you can't use this power
But the ice stone is mine now
I brought you back to life temporarily because we had no other choice.
So it's a stone
able to prevent the transformation of a nomad
We must find him and destroy him
We must destroy all the nomads, and he brings them back to life
His strength is truly terrifying.
But this...
Uk, they will soon find out about your punishment,
so you can't go back
Stay home for a while
Okay, Moo Deok and I will go home
Try not to get noticed by Jin Moo
Yes
Let's go
He will get rid of the stone as soon as he receives it
We need to find him sooner
Kil Joo was right
Stone in the palace
So Dan Zhu, who owns the stone...
this is that person
Deal with everything quietly
I will send the court lady Han instead
Will you send messages through it?
I understand you
Because of what happened, Sosnovy Bor will now suspect me
This happened because you underestimated Chan Wook
I didn't think he would free himself so quickly
He is a genius who instantly mastered Ryusu
He was born with the energy of the King's star
I didn't immediately begin to underestimate him
I thought he was special
since he was born under the sign of such a star
However, Chan Wook turned out to be a complete disappointment
He was a simple boy, nothing special
Angry at the world, he hid his helplessness and laziness
under the mask of composure. He never had a goal
He was just a noble young man with high self-esteem,
so it was enough to serve him
So he has changed
I thought he was weak
But he opened the gates of energy by drinking poison
Thought he was just a braggart, but he really beat the Crown Prince
What made him change so much?
People change
for the sake of other people
Find the one who appeared in his life shortly before all the changes
This will be the answer
Chan Wook was rejected by twelve teachers, but he still found his way
Who could help him with this?
Teacher, can we go to Danhyangok right away?
Thanks to my punishment we have time
Let's practice in Danhyangok
We can try to climb that tree
It's very cold in Danhyangok right now
If we get stuck there because of the snow,
we may die of hunger
I thought it was warm in winter and there was plenty of food
You told Yulia that last time
I said that to calm him down
He was worried that his tame bird had a hard time in the winter,
that's why I lied
Are you talking about the bird he called with his whistle when he was in Danhyangok?
Did Jin Moo almost kill Wook?
I apologized for Uka and took him away from there
But Jin Moo might try to harm him
Fortunately, I insisted that we fix the constellation bowl,
so we will have access to Jeonbugwan
You will go to Jeonbugwan with the workers of Sosnovy Bor
and you will look after Jin Mu
- Yes
San Ho
I heard Moo Deok was in Jeonbugwan too
Is she okay?
Yes
The nomad who went wild and turned to stone
really came back to life?
Therefore, the head had to return without saying anything
How did Uk react to this?
He didn't seem surprised
He asked the head if the ice stone could
bring the soul swallower back to life
It seems he already knew about it
This means that he personally saw how the nomad came to life
The head told him that they need to be destroyed
And nomads and stone
Get rid of everything that is evil
And what did Uk answer to this?
This is just my guess
but he doesn't seem to agree with it
Chan Wook is always carefree and carefree
But this is not the way to treat dark magic.
You and Uk are close
You should warn him
Danhyangok is not only cold,
there's no one there at all
We can't be alone now
Why is this suddenly?
I'm afraid
that I will absorb your energy
You haven't gone wild. Nothing happened, even after our contact
Because I absorbed that eunuch's energy
Everything's fine now
but we don't know when it might happen again
If necessary,
you can run away or kill me
But if I absorb your energy
I can't stand this
What's so funny?
Are you having fun?
No, that's not the point
My heart fluttered
These are your words
carry more meaning than "I missed you"
The Shadow Warrior finally answered
to my naive and sincere declaration of love
I'll find a stone
so you never have to absorb my energy
You'll have to go against Park Jin
Then I'll be just as strong
You lost nine battles in a row to the magicians of Jeongjingak.
Arrogant
Exactly, yin-yang jade. I have to return it
But how did you call the Crown Prince?
There is one way...
It makes my heart beat wildly
Chan Wook, the alleged offender, did not have a sword
But Jin Moo had it, although he insisted on his innocence
Mister
Master Li, what brings you here?
Why are you not in Sosnovy Bor, but at home?
He is punished
Punished? For what?
What have you done this time?
No, it's not like that
Maid Kim, don't worry so much
It's like...
fake punishment
It's more of a vacation disguised as a punishment.
It's true
Glad to hear
Then we'll go fishing on Lake Gyeongjeongdaeho
Great idea
You should relax here after spending time with Mr. Chan
You can't, maid Kim. I can't slack off now
Master Li, I'm sorry.
I've already lost nine out of ten battles
There's one last chance to win
I'm going to train. I hope for your understanding
You suddenly became so diligent
Yes, my goal is to make Maid Kim proud of me.
I can't sit back and fish
Lately your words touch my soul
Okay
Go ahead and train
And I will cook you sweets
Tell the truth, why were you punished?
I broke the cup of constellations in Jeonbugwan
Don't tell that to maid Kim
I saw lightning strike right over Jeonbugwan
I guess she hit the cup
We can't tell you the details, but the owner is not to blame for anything
The head of Sosnovy Bor will tell you the rest
I'll lend you my fishing rods
I used to love fishing
I have a couple of very good ones.
I'll bring it now
It's a pity
I wanted to teach him how to catch goldfish
Goldfish?
You're talking about the one that can only be caught
in Gyeongcheongdaeho Lake?
Do you know what this is?
I've heard about her. Fish that is formed from the energy of the lake
I heard that only magicians who have mastered Chisu or higher can catch her
You really know a lot
When you caught that fish and you're in control
energy of Gyeongcheongdaeho Lake...
Pleasant feeling
Share this with the owner
He's busy
Master Li
Master Li, take a look
This is the best fishing rod, it's made of bamboo...
He's not busy, starting tomorrow
he will go fishing with you
What are you talking about? I need to train
Now you should not hold a sword, but a fishing rod
Go to Gyeongjeongdaeho Lake and catch a Golden Fish
What?
Seems like a good place
No no, Master Li
I've fished here before. The water is very cold
There are no fish here because they have nothing to eat.
And we took bad fishing rods
Goldfish must be caught with a fishing rod that bends easily
Just like this one
Is this fish bait?
These are sweets
Maid Kim collected them for Master Lee
Maid Kim is a very kind woman
Where's the bait?
We need worms or small fish
What?
Do you fish without bait?
I told you that Goldfish feed on energy.
My energy will go along the bamboo stick
and will serve as bait
Your energy?
Master, repeat after the master
Now
Now you just need to control the energy of the lake
and wait for the golden fish to bite
Moo Deok
I feel like a fool. Do I have to continue?
I took the bait!
This is the Golden Fish
This is a clot of water that is formed from the energy of the lake
Only those who have mastered Chisu or higher, capable of controlling water,
they can catch her
I haven't fished for a long time
But I have to admit, it's still exciting to catch a Goldfish
So it's not a real fish?
Master Li didn't bring you here to fish.
He is here to help you master Chisu
Only those who have the strength
can catch a clot of energy from Lake Gyeongcheongdaeho
and master Chisu
Chisu?
Slowly
No, you're in too much of a hurry. Slowly
- Slowly
- No
Jeonbugwan must have found another blind girl
Cho Young says they bring blind girls
from all over the country every day
- Let's go in
- Yes
So you are saying
that perhaps there are nomads in every family,
who participated in the murder of Nak Soo's father,
and we need to use Jinyeowon's relics,
to find them?
We were going to wait until the nomad
from Degantongun will come to consciousness,
but we can't wait any longer
The point is that
last night we found another one
I heard
A nomad who was a eunuch was found in Jeonbugwan
Jin Moo must have already visited you.
My brother Jin Mu said that Pine Forest sent a burglar to Jeonbugwan,
who tried to set him up. He was very upset
To find out whether Jin Mu is guilty or not,
we need the relics and powers of the head of Jinyeowon
Help us
Sorry,
but I refuse
There is nothing more shameful for a magician than being accused of using dark magic.
If we will
test magicians with their relics without any evidence,
we'll only make people hate Jinyeowon
I heard Jin Moo
looking for your eldest daughter
He asked you not to help Sosnovy Bor
in exchange for help finding your daughter?
- This has nothing to do with...
- No, it has
Your behavior towards Sosnovy Bor has suddenly changed
Do you want me to always do what you ask?
Is this the kind of behavior you expect?
Jinyoungwon disobeys
Pine forest
- Head Jin!
- Go away
I have an appointment
When they find your big sister
there will be no more barriers to our love
Because Sosnovy Bor and Jinyeowon have good relations
Oh, that's right...
Here
This is the decoration I liked last time
Someone already bought it
How did you get it?
Paid that man four times the amount
Thought you'd like it
I really like it
Your happy smile
makes me the happiest in the world
Why does uncle look so upset?
Did something happen?
I think he had a big fight with the head of Jinyeowon.
I drew a dark red mole behind her ear.
As a child, Boo Young fell. She has a scar on her left arm
About a third of a finger long
This is necessary for you to become Jin Bu Young, be patient.
Every scar, every mole...
Any little thing her mother can remember
Okay
I'll pour acid on your skin to make the scar more visible.
What kind of fish is Young Master Chan trying to catch?
All he does is go to the lake
I need to take them food
I will ask servant Li to carry
And you stay and help me
We need to clean the house and prepare food for the memorial service.
For whose?
A young girl who died a terrible death
She was mad at our family
that's why I want to hold a wake for her
Maid Kim
I returned from the temple
- Okay
- Here
Buddhist monk wrote a speech
What a wonderful speech
But where are their names?
I should have written down the names of the spirits
Here they are
Right here. Cho Chun and Cho Young
Cho Young? This is my name
Oh, that's it. Now I see
Cho Chun and Cho Young
Wonderful speech
Servant Li, come with me
Take the food to the master
Yes, of course
Maid Kim conducts a wake
for me and my father?
They brought us rice with mushrooms. My favorite
Maid Kim is a great cook
It's biting! I caught it!
I hooked a worm. She fell for him
We can eat it
Here we go...
Hold
Take your time
One day you will feel this feeling
when the goldfish bites
This will be Chisu - the ability to control energy
Clear
Master Li, you taught me to read "Words of the Heart"
Why do you keep helping me?
By chance for no reason
which should be kept secret?
It's none of your business
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
This concerns my family
It's because of the maid Kim, right?
You constantly shower her with compliments.
And you also have a scarf around your neck...
He's from the shop she goes to.
This is her gift, right?
And most importantly,
I saw dried wildflowers in Kim's maid's room
Danhyangok is full of them
And this is your gift, right?
- Yes, it's true
- So I knew it
But you practice chastity...
I don’t have “those” feelings for her!
I think she's beautiful and kind-hearted
That's all
It's the same as confessing your feelings for her
Relationships between men and women are always “like this”
And what about yourself?
You are a man and Moo Deok is a woman. What's between you?
As for me...
I like her
I can't believe I'm saying this to someone who practices chastity.
Only the maid Kim already likes someone
I hope I didn't hurt your feelings
I also have to say
I heard Moo Deok likes Yul
Dan Gu told you this? What kind of conversation is this worldly?
I'm not just messing around with you here
I realized that worldly talk...
sometimes they are useful
Thanks to the story of Julia's first love,
I was able to find out about Nak Soo, the killer
The girl he met in Danhyangok
turned out to be Nak Soo
He realized that it was her...
because of the whistle given to them. He lay next to her body
I know you overheard my conversation with Jin in Saejukwon
Therefore, you yourself know about the history of Nak Su
Come home early today
Maid Kim conducts a wake...
for a little girl who died a terrible death
That's all
Constellation bowl set
Take your servants back to Sosnovy Bor
No, not perfect yet
We like everything
What do you think?
Just take a look
Bowl and stem colors are different
Need to change the leg
We've changed it many times already.
We like everything
The head of Sosnovy Bor promised
that everything will return as it was
You can't make mistakes
Usually it takes no more than two days
But this time everything was somehow delayed
Don't you like us coming here?
Why would that be?
I just think Sosnovy Bor is wasting time and money.
Don't worry about Sosnovy Bor's money
Yul, last time we met, I noted your skills
Already mastered Chisu?
Yes
It turns out that you are the first magician of Jeonjingak,
possessed Chisu
Just like my father. Seo Il must be very proud of you
Is he the magician of Jeongjingak?
You can't drag a person against his will
Can you stand up?
What are you looking at?
Is he the magician of Jeongjingak?
- His name is Seo Yul?
- Yes
They are the sons of noble families, not your cup of tea
Stop wandering around here, sit quietly
Maybe the thief So Yi is no match for him
But once I become Jin Bu Young, the future head of Jinyoung,
everything can change
This is for Master Chan's friend and his daughter
Their bodies were not buried
and hardly anyone remembers them
Therefore, I will hold at least one service
Maid Kim
Thank you
What?
They would be very grateful to you
I'm sure they are very grateful
Glad to hear that
Do not extinguish incense sticks until they burn out
Cho Chun, Cho Young
Father...
Mister Chan went fishing
He'll be back soon, you can wait inside
Did Moo Deok go with him?
No, she's at home
Helped with the wake
Cho Chun, Cho Young
If I hadn't left you...
one in the mountains
you wouldn't have to hold back your tears right now
and pretend to be someone else
But even now
I can't come...
and tell you that I know who you are
Cho Chun, Cho Young
Are the sticks burnt out?
Yes
Burned out
Have you been sitting here?
Let's clean everything up
When did you return? I heard you went fishing
Yes, just got back
Are you alone? Where is Dan Gu?
He has some business to attend to. I think he's dating someone
How's that?
Why did you come?
The head said you can come back
Faster than I thought
Sit down, let's have a drink. I still needed to talk to you
I can't, I'm sorry
- I need to return to Sosnovy Bor
- Yes?
Then we'll talk later, in Jeonjingak
You will be very surprised
Uk, I'll be back to Soho Fortress soon
I promised my father that I would stay in Jeongjingak
until I master Chisu
Master Ho wrote a letter to his father,
so soon he will tell me to come back
Then I'll have to leave
But Soho fortress is very far away
Dan Gu and I will miss you so much
I want to take with me
someone
- Who?
- I can’t say yet
I'll tell you when the time comes
I'll go. See you tomorrow
Okay. Bye
Because I was bored
I really liked this man
Nomads can only recover by sucking out someone else’s energy.
Having done this once,
they turn into monsters
And our task is
protect the world from them
Does Yul really know everything?
I want to take with me
someone
Owner
What?
Has Seo Yul already left? Maid Kim gave it to him
Looks like he was talking about you
Who? Did Seo Yul say something?
I can go back
Is that why you're so upset?
When you return to the forest,
your duel with Cha Bum will take place
Are you afraid to lose?
I won't lose tomorrow
I finally got it done
Today is Chan Wook's last fight
We have slightly changed the betting conditions
Winner of today's match
will receive not a golden toad, but something else
Winner
win the maid
I agreed to serve him
who will win today
- What's going on?
- Excellent
Chan Wook's last opponent
come forward
Chan Wook
Today to fight with you
I'll be there
Thanks for watching with us!
doramamania
Alchemy
Shower
Uk can bring chaos to this world
What happens if he attracts attention?
We need to choose the one who will definitely win
I'll win and take her with me as a maid
Has he mastered the techniques of the previous nine opponents?
I have to find him
Then you have to lose something
Your quivering love did not give in to anyone
Only then will I be able to look into his eyes without shame
Ask around about Moo Deok. What kind of girl is she
“A look filled with tenderness”, same for me
You don't consider me a woman
- Don’t regret it later
- Okay, go ahead!
I really like you, master